bigfile.to 2017-03-10

# Bigfile.to - #1 Easy & Fast File Storage

This privacy policy (hereafter referred to as "Policy") explains how personally identifiable information is collected, used and disclosed by bigfile.to ("we" or "us") with respect to your access and use of bigfile's online file storage and sharing service located at www.bigfile.to , (hereafter referred to as the "Service"), so you can make a well informed decision about using the Service.

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on this Policy the date it was last updated. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to review this Policy from time-to-time to make sure that you fully understand how any personally identifiable information you provide to us or collected about you will be used.

* ## What Is Personal Information?

As used in this Policy, the term "personally identifiable information" refers to information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, username or email address), or information about that individual that is directly linked to other specific identifying information. Personally identifiable information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Service or about a group or category of services or users. Data collected in this manner contains no references to individual identities or other personally identifiable information. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.

* ## What Information Do We Collect?

Active Collection: We collect information from you in various ways when you use the Service. For example, we collect information: (i) that you voluntarily provide to us (basic information as provided when contacting us via email); and (ii) to which you explicitly provide us access to and publicly disclose. Such information may include personal identifiable information, such as your name, email address, date of birth, social network data and performance related data. Personal and demographic information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with posting data, providing access to your online groups and other activities in connection with the Service.

Passive Collection: When you use the Service, some information is also automatically collected, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, browser type, the address of a referring website, and your activity on the Service. We may also automatically collect certain logistical information in server logs, including information about how you use various features of the Service and information regarding the number, frequency and length of each individual session. We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" when you use the Service.  
Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive at the request of a website. Among other things, cookies help us to dramatically improve and enhance the Service along with the user experience. If we link cookies to any personally identifiable information, we will treat this information as personally identifiable information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your individual browser settings to learn about these functions. However, please note that the removal of rejection of cookies might adversely impact certain features or service that are available to you.

Please be aware that the use of cookies by our partners or external websites is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.  
We may use also use Web beacons or similar technology on the Service and in any of our Apps (where applicable). Please note that we do not tie the information gathered to our customers??personally identifiable information. Web beacons are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on the Service or in emails relating to the Service, these are used to collect certain information and monitor user activity on the Service, such as counting visits and to give us a better understanding of the overall effectiveness and Service operations. Such technologies are used to collect aggregate statistics related to usage of the Service and do not collect personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information will be stored on secured servers, and we may store and process personally identifiable information in the United States and other countries.

* ## How Do We Use the Personally Identifiable Information We Collect?

We use personally identifiable information collected through the Service for the purposes described in this Policy or elsewhere on the Service or in our Apps. For example, we may use personally identifiable information we collect in the following ways:

  1. To process and complete any transactions in connection with the Service and Apps.
  2. To request feedback and to otherwise contact you about your use of the Service and Apps.
  3. To respond to your emails, questions, comments, requests and complaints; as well as to provide customer service.
  4. To monitor and analyze Service usage and trends.
  5. To personalize and improve the Service, and our users' experiences with the Service (such as providing new or revised content or features that match user interests), and to increase the Service's functionality and user friendliness;
  6. To send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, additional information about our products and services and support and administrative messages, and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Service. When sending marketing information about our services or products, we will only use your email address provided during registration. We will not use other email addresses you may have provided to us, for instance in a feedback form, to send marketing emails;
  7. To notify you about important changes to the Service and related Apps.

* ## What Personally Identifiable Information Do We Share With Third-Parties?

We will not knowingly share the personally identifiable information we collect from you through the Service with third-parties, except as described in this Policy or on the Service. For example, we may share personally identifiable information in the following circumstances:

  1. With vendors, consultants, and other service providers such as a credit card processing company (to bill you for services), a forum provider (for hosting our public forums), and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf ("Service Providers"). When you sign up for our services we will share your personal information only as necessary to the third parties required to provide the Service.
  2. When you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you on the Service that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.
  3. In an aggregated or anonymous form that does not directly identify you.
  4. When we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary, or appropriate to comply with the law, or legal processes, or to respond to lawful requests or legal authorities including, but not limited to, responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants, or court orders.
  5. When we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of bigfile including our users and employees as well as copyright owners, third-parties or the public. This also extents to protecting bigfile. or our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate, or otherwise unlawful use of the Service.
  6. To enforce or apply this Policy, the Terms, or our other policies or agreements.
  7. In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition. Or in any other situation where personally identifiable information may be disclosed or transferred as one of the business assets of bigfile. By using this Service you automatically give consent in the understanding that any information you provide, gain access to or share with other individuals through the Service will be available to other users and in some cases may be publicly available.

We are not responsible for the actions of Service Providers or other third-parties, nor shall we be responsible for any additional information you provide to any other users or third- parties. We strongly encourage you to become familiar with third-party privacy practices before disclosing information directly to any such party. Nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregated or anonymous information, which may be shared with third-parties without your consent.

* ## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to make use of our Service, you may correct, update or delete your information as you see fit by making the change in your bigfile account profile or by emailing our Customer Support at . We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.  
If you wish to request the deletion of an unauthorized profile that is using your personal information you may contact us at .

Please note that we will only retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed, in order to provide you with our services. We will retain and use your information as necessary in compliance with our legal obligations or to resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

* ## Links to Other Websites

The Service may contain links to other websites. Any personally identifiable information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third-party and is subject to that third-party's individual Privacy Policy. Please note that this Policy for bigfile does not apply to such linked websites, and we are not responsible for the content, privacy, security practices and policies of these websites or any other websites that are linked to/from the Service. We strongly encourage you to become familiar with third-party their privacy and security practices / policies before providing them with personally identifiable information.

* ## What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information Online?

We take sufficient measures to protect your personally identifiable information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or truly impenetrable. As a result no method of data transmission can guarantee against any interception or any other type of misuse. To assist with the protection of personally identifiable information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are solely responsible for all uses of the Service and Apps by any person using your account. Please notify us immediately if you believe your password has been compromised. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at .

* ## Advertising

We may partner with a third-party ad network to display advertising within our service. Our ad network partners use Web beacons and log files to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on our service, in order to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.

* ## Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Service may include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook 'Like' button and Widgets, such as the 'Share This' button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and also may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third-party or hosted directly on our Site. However, your interactions with these Features are governed solely by the privacy policy of the company providing the service.

* ## What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Use of Your Information?

You may choose to "opt out" of receiving marketing or promotional emails from us by following the instructions in relevant promotional emails. You may also opt out of such marketing emails by following the instructions within such emails or emailing us at .  
However, if you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, regarding your account or our ongoing business relations.

* ## Questions?

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at .
